We need to have the man in City Council for today's date.
Adam too is public input and unscheduled personal characteristics, as well as the audits that wishes to address the council on any of the agenda.
We'll do it.
I need to start over when we get it.
All right.
Thanks for that reminder.
Adam too is public input and unscheduled personal parents.
I think I just said that.
I don't see anybody beat in a trail to the lectern.
So we'll go to item three, which is a consent agenda staff who's recommending items four through 11 for the consent agenda.
If there are no questions on any of those items of intertraining motion to approve.
I'll do it.
Yep.
Okay.
And second.
How's it going?
We'll call a police.
Johnson.
Mirrors type.
West state.
Aye.
Forester.
Short.
12, which is new business.
And there's no business for the council meeting.
Any minute or.
Council committee announcements.
You don't got one.
Why should you do that?
Why?
Good for you.
No good.
Six spots for us.
August 13.
See you.
My list will pull.
One came.
I have this after Easter.
One being the 5th.
And by dollar.
And commission fee.
It's the.
I was going to get that to pull.
Bull rills must provide.
Print for rave and vacuum.
Laces and color.
Car.
And be curious to our fellow.
So now this is the dog who's got blackly normally think of for.
If I please the staff, this is to take your bags filming with us.
Will be the swimming pool.
If you want.
And maybe a good.
Will.
If you don't have.
Cool.
No.
If you're.
It's an affinity for water dancing, so all this 13 at one peak from one to five p.m.
Any other announcements?
I got one quick.
I was trying to look at the day that I believe will have another scheduled meeting before then,
but the memory is certainly correct.
I believe school starts the 17th.
My favorite thing is we'll have another one, but as always I always like to let everybody know
that anybody else, people remember how kids are going to be moving, kids are going to be trying to get to school,
and some of them might be walking, some of them might be riding a bike.
So heads up.
Okay.
Sort of 17.
I'll see you in a minute.
A couple of quick things.
The day after the spots flash is going to be the official day that the renovation of the Civic Center begins.
So one thing we wanted to tell people is the kind of the staging area for this project is going to be our west parking lot,
and also the utility.
need drop box during this time is going to be on fifth street. So that's going to be one of the
major issues for the public now that will still be able to come in the front door and go to our
public service counters. Other than that we're going to be this is going to be a construction area
of our head only if you want to go into. So we're kind of happy to get this project underway but we'll get
through it and look forward to the end of the project. So say that about the drop box. It's been drop
box again is going to be relocated to fifth avenue in the Civic Center. So the customer will still
have access to a drop box of this via the street. That's correct. That's correct. The second thing
is that we are currently working with Tony Holden to have a box of equipment on the 21st of August
in front of the Coleman Theatre. Some details are 25. Oh sorry, I had 21st, 25. But anyway, this is
form we're days to get ready for. So anyway we're working very closely with Tony on that.
If that I think our goal is to have a press conference about that on Thursday at the Coleman. So we're
going to be cooperating to get that done. I think all the staff members remember when that was done
about 15 years ago was a lot of fun and a big success. So it's fun to bring something like that back
down town. Those are nice. All right. Item 15 is your session pursuant to 25.OS subsection
307B for a purpose of the conference of communications between city council and attorney concern depending
litigation to win. My name is properties LLC or city of Marama. And then you had something you need to
add. Yes. So it would be my recommendation that this needs to be discussed in executive session
and not in an open meeting. Okay. Do we have a motion to go into executive session for the reasons
listed make motion. And second. Second. Well Paul. Western. For Mr. Lewis. Hi. Johnson. So for those of you that
might be interested, there's the only two remaining items or the German, there's no action items or anything
so when we come back we're just going to journey go home. So if you want to wait you can. If you want to go home
yeah. I'm a place about to wait. They heard about one more to one here. And I'm about to wait.
I'm not going home. I'm not going home. The next thing to do is stuff.
Who's that? Who? Who's that? Who's that? Who's that? What is that extension about? Why?
He's that. Oh. You can't understand that one. They are nice people.
Is this something we're supposed to look at? It's for day.
So, I mentioned our meal and, you know, I was supposed to meet today and hide it the way
that all fits a cancel.
But this is just some preliminary stuff that you can put together.
We'll still have our meeting and then we'll tell you from now.
That's what I'm saying.
Yeah, I mean actually, it'll be a tip for a ban for next year too, I mean we're so close.
We've tried to have a process for everybody.
Ben and Chuck and Ben and Darryl's in 5th and 30th of the year.
We're going to, we are going to, what a well we've been.
Are we coming out of the MSU-F-A-R-S-S?
Do we, we didn't need the vote to come out of the recess, so now what we need to do is a
talk.
Just note that no action was taken, on the MSU-F-R, we're back at 751,
and we're going to the next agenda item which is to adjourn MSU-A and then,
the next agenda item is adjourned.
So item 4 could impact the MSU-A is adjourned.
Something's over here.
Great.
Sycommunists?
No, Paul.
Lewis, I Westminster, John Furocratic, Shawer, Jonathan Schultz.
We are also back as the Council now.
now and it is 752 there's no action taken and item 16 is adjournment that we have most of the
chance to adjourn.